{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","address":"2901 Grand River ","zipcode":"48201-34","owner":"Bruce Dall","licenseNumber":"208230","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/13/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000C0C4681B54C454C088CEAABD722B4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43179","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","inspectionDate":"2018-08-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43179","inspectionDate":"8/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"6-403.11","violationDescription":"(A) Areas designated for EMPLOYEES to eat, drink, and use tobacco shall be located so that FOOD, EQUIPMENT, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES are protected from contamination.\r\n(B) Lockers or other suitable facilities shall be located in a designated room or area where contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES can not occur.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Locker(s)/employee storage area(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Contaminates","subProblem":"Equipment","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Relocate to a designated area that does not contaminate items or surfaces."},{"inspectionid":"43179","inspectionDate":"8/10/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-08-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."}]},{"inspectionid":"41214","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","inspectionDate":"2018-01-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41214","inspectionDate":"1/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"41214","inspectionDate":"1/11/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"At the Frozen drink machine","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"39225","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","inspectionDate":"2017-07-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"39225","inspectionDate":"7/13/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-07-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"39225","inspectionDate":"7/13/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Commercially processed ready to eat potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-07-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"inspectionid":"39225","inspectionDate":"7/13/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Equipment/utensils","location":"BAR (MAIN)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-07-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"inspectionid":"39225","inspectionDate":"7/13/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"EQUIPMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-07-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"37337","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","inspectionDate":"2016-12-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37337","inspectionDate":"12/8/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"37337","inspectionDate":"12/8/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"37337","inspectionDate":"12/8/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\r\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."}]},{"inspectionid":"37107","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","inspectionDate":"2016-11-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inspectorid":"83","pcount":"2","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37107","inspectionDate":"11/10/2016","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"37107","inspectionDate":"11/10/2016","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"4680","name":"Motor City Casino - Pit Stop Bar","violationCode":"5-402.13","violationDescription":"SEWAGE shall be conveyed to the point of disposal through an APPROVED sanitary SEWAGE system or other system, including use of SEWAGE transport vehicles, waste retention tanks, pumps, pipes, hoses, and connections that are constructed, maintained, and operated according to LAW.(P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sewage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not conveyed to point of disposal","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-10T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements above."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"4680"}}